{
    "subject": "resource/Georg_Grimpe",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Leipzig",
    "human_readable": "Georg Grimpe was born in Leipzig.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.893731415271759,
            "question": "What is Leipzig known for besides being the birthplace of Georg Grimpe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8898653984069824,
            "question": "Where was Georg Grimpe born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7484676241874695,
            "question": "Besides Georg Grimpe, who else might be from Leipzig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7319996356964111,
            "question": "Can you tell me the birthplace of Georg Grimpe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6839783787727356,
            "question": "What city is associated with Georg Grimpe's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5698710083961487,
            "question": "Are there any famous individuals born in Leipzig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4773329794406891,
            "question": "In which German city did Georg Grimpe come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4321114122867584,
            "question": "If someone was born in Leipzig, what cultural influences might they have experienced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18639123439788818,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Leipzig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16400285065174103,
            "question": "Is Leipzig a historically significant city in Germany?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Georg Grimpe was born in Leipzig.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8426_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some interesting facts about Leipzig?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8426_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If someone was born in Leipzig, what cultural influences might they have experienced?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8426_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which German city did Georg Grimpe come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8426_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8426_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8426_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8426_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8426_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8426_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8426_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8426_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8426_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8426_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8426_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Georg Grimpe was born in Leipzig\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because there is no mention of George Grimpe's birthplace being Leipzig. In fact, I couldn't find any specific information about his birthdate or place in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not contain any information about Georg Grimpe being born in Leipzig. Instead, it provides biographical details including his name and some aspects of his life but does not mention the place of his birth."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Georg Grimpe was born in Wilpischen near K\u00f6nigsberg (now the Russian enclave of Kaliningrad), not Leipzig.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states Georg Hermann Stenzleit was born in Wilpischen near K\u00f6nigsberg (now the Russian enclave of Kaliningrad) on 23rd July 1848.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Georg Grimpe being born in Leipzig in the provided context information, but rather a mention of his entry in Deutsche Biographische Enzyklop\u00e4die Online, edited by Rudolf Vierhaus, which does not provide any information about his place of birth.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Leipzig as the birthplace of Georg Grimpe. It provides details about his life, including his profession as a cabinet maker and his political activities, but there is no information indicating he was born in Leipzig.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}